What? Are you back?
ماذا؟  هل عدت؟
What? Be my maid of honor.
ماذا؟  كوني خادمتي الشرف.
Yes, I'm getting married soon.
نعم ، سأتزوج قريبًا.
No, that's not the point.
لا ، هذا ليس بيت القصيد.
You said you weren't coming back.
قلت إنك لن تعود.
You don't want to see that person.
أنت لا تريد أن ترى هذا الشخص.
Are you sure this is okay?
هل أنت متأكد من أن هذا جيد؟
Don't worry.
لا تقلق.
Didn't you send me the makeup schedule?
ألم ترسل لي جدول الماكياج؟
By the way, don't forget.
بالمناسبة ، لا تنسى.
You must wear a girlfriend's outfit when you meet.
يجب أن ترتدي زي صديقة عندما تقابل.
A sister is bigger than the sky.
الأخت أكبر من السماء.
I don't think so.
أنا لا أعتقد ذلك.
Mom, where are we going?
أمي ، إلى أين نحن ذاهبون؟
Honey, be good. Wait a second.
عزيزتي ، كوني جيدة.  انتظر لحظة.
Let's give Mrs. Orange a surprise, okay?
دعونا نعطي السيدة أورانج مفاجأة ، حسنًا؟
What? You said you didn't have time.
ماذا؟  قلت أنه ليس لديك وقت.
Who are we going to marry?
من سوف نتزوج؟
You said you wanted to try on a best man costume and I had to work with you.
قلت إنك تريد تجربة زي أفضل رجل وكان علي أن أعمل معك.
I'm too busy.
أنا مشغول جدا.
That's a lot of nonsense.
هذا كثير من الهراء.
I don't care.
لا أهتم.
Or you can come now. I'll send you the address.
أو يمكنك المجيء الآن.  سأرسل لك العنوان.
That's it. Bye.
هذا هو.  وداعا.
feed
تغذية
Come down.
إهدأ.
I'm here.
أنا هنا.
Why are you here? I've been waiting for you.
لماذا أنت هنا؟  انا كنت في انتظارك.
Hello, orange.
مرحبا برتقالي.
Are you looking for me?
هل تبحث عني؟
Ah, I'm back now.
آه ، لقد عدت الآن.
How are you?
كيف حالك؟
You still can't talk.
ما زلت لا تستطيع التحدث.
this
هذه
Is it your child?
هل هو طفلك؟
This time,
هذا الوقت،
Are you still leaving?
هل مازلت راحل؟
I've been looking for you for a long time.
لقد كنت أبحث عنك لفترة طويلة.
Ling Chen, what are you doing?
لينغ تشين ، ماذا تفعل؟
Well, I suddenly remembered I have something to do.
حسنًا ، تذكرت فجأة أن لدي شيئًا أفعله.
orange
البرتقالي
I've been waiting for you for a long time.
لقد كنت في انتظارك لفترة طويلة.
Let's go together.
لنذهب معا.
This is
هذا هو
Xia Yan, aunt.
شيا يان ، عمة.
Hello, Mrs. Orange.
مرحبا سيدة أورانج.
With whom?
مع من؟
You can't even eat.
لا يمكنك حتى أن تأكل.
Hello, Uncle.
مرحبا يا عم.
Hi, dad.
مرحبا أبي.
Why do you call me father?
لماذا تناديني يا أبي؟
Mom said that.
قالت أمي ذلك.
What else did I tell you?
ماذا قلت لك ايضا؟
Mom also said that
قالت أمي ذلك أيضًا
Dad's name is...
اسم أبي هو ...
Lin Zeyan.
لين زيان.
You're already three months pregnant.
أنت بالفعل حامل في شهرها الثالث.
Why don't you have a good rest?
لماذا لا تحصل على قسط جيد من الراحة؟
Can't you see me?
الا تستطيع رؤيتي
Hello. Alright. I'll be right there.
مرحبًا.  على ما يرام.  سأكون هناك.
Ah
آه
Xia Yan, will Mrs. Orange take you to play?
شيا يان ، هل تأخذك السيدة أورانج لتلعب؟
Do not
لاتفعل
Xia Yan, please.
شيا يان ، من فضلك.
I'll find you later.
سأجدك لاحقًا.
Well
نحن سوف
Let's go somewhere.
هيا نذهب إلى مكان ما.
When are you going to tell me the truth?
متى ستقول لي الحقيقة؟
You know everything.
أنت تعرف كل شيء.
Am I so untrustworthy?
هل أنا غير جدير بالثقة؟
I'm just scared.
أنا خائفة فقط.
Qin Luoluo and the company will hurt you.
سوف يؤذيك تشين Luoluo والشركة.
After all, my eyes haven't healed yet.
بعد كل شيء ، عيني لم تلتئم بعد.
So I dare not bet your happiness.
لذلك لا أجرؤ على الرهان على سعادتك.
Why don't you let me face it with you?
لماذا لا تدعني أواجه الأمر معك؟
I didn't dare to take the risk.
لم أجرؤ على المخاطرة.
When I think of you being hurt,
عندما أفكر في أنك تتأذى ،
I'm really scared.
أنا خائفة حقا.
You fool.
يالك من أحمق.
I thought you gave the ring to someone else.
اعتقدت أنك أعطيت الخاتم لشخص آخر.
It only belongs to you.
إنه ملك لك فقط.
I won't let you escape this time.
لن أدعك تهرب هذه المرة.
Hey, wait a second.
مهلا ، انتظر ثانية.
What about your gossiping girlfriends on the news?
ماذا عن صديقاتك القيل والقال في الأخبار؟
actor
الممثل
Why are you looking for an actress?
لماذا تبحث عن ممثلة؟
The kind you pay for?
النوع الذي تدفع ثمنه؟
Group acting
مجموعة التمثيل
Be more serious this time.
كن أكثر جدية هذه المرة.
Mrs. Lin.
السيدة لين.